# Apitsada Suan-ngarm

SENIOR SOFTWARE ENGINEER

🛮 (+66) 83-823-0573 | 💌 fei.apitsada@gmail.com | 🖸 feiiydu | 🛅 feiiydu | 📢 feiiydu





# Summary.

A Senior Software Engineer with 6 years of experience using Golang to design and develop scalable microservice for high-traffic web and mobile application base on business requirement, Strong in performance-focused architecture and tools like MongoDB, MySQL and Redis. Looking to continue to develop my skill set on the back-end with Golang

# Work Experience

### **Senior Software Engineer (Golang Developer)**

Jan. 2022 - Now

Thailand

**BITKUB ONLINE** 

- Made microservice for Bitkub application and www.bitkub.com
- Design and implement microservice system
  - Notifcation service notify to user by SMS (8\*8), Email (SendGrid) and Line
  - User report service generate yearl transaction report for user
  - **Passkey service** passwordless authentication with WebAuthn
  - **2FA service** generate key, verify code with Vault TOTP
  - Fee credit service calculate and process user's fee credit in bitkub system
  - Digital signing service digital signing file XML and PDF for business purpose
  - **Dividend service** distributing dividends to customers holding coin with dividend conditions
- Enhance the feature e.g. Bitkub Reward, KUB Convert
- · Implement microservice integrate with MySQL, MongoDB, DataDogTracer, OpenTelemetry, RabbitMQ, Vault TOTP
- · Investigate and Support Incident
- Senior Software Engineer (Jan. 2024 Now)
- Software Engineer (Jan. 2022 Dec. 2023)

## Software Engineer (Golang/iOS Developer)

Jun. 2018 - Dec. 2021

Thailand

KASIKORN BUSINESS-TECHNOLOGY GROUP (KBTG)

- Made microservice for K+Shop backend using 'Golang' connecting with MongoDB, Elasticsearch
- Implement QR Credit Card for K+shop Application
- Implement SPoC (Software-Based PIN on COTS) for K+shop Application
- Investigate and Support Incident
- Scrum Master (Aug. 2020 Dec. 2021): Facilitate agile ceremony meeting, Resource planning
- iOS Developer (Jun. 2018 Dec. 2018): Develop K+SHOP application in a frontend side, UX/UI

#### **Cooperative Education program**

Jul. - Dec. 2017

ExxonMobil

Thailand

- Make chat-bot on SKYPE for Business for Database Administration and Management team call "DBAM Bot" Automatically answer frequently asked questions. Using C# programming with Visual Studio.
- Working in global environment with Brazilian co-worker.

Internship program May. - Jun. 2017

THE UNIVERSITY OF ELECTRO-COMMUNICATIONS

Tokyo, Japan

- Cooperative with Japanese students to make gripper robot hand which can catch any object by using SolidWorks to design, 3D printer to printout and control by motors and switches.
- Exchange knowledge and culture with foreign friends.

## **Education**

#### **B.S.** in Computer Engineering

Aug. 2014 - May. 2018

Bangkok, Thailand

KING MONGKUT'S INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY LADKRABANG (KMITL)

- · Majoring in Information Engineering
- · First Class Honors
- Thesis: Skype Bot for Database Administration
- · Learned programming (C Java Python), Telecommunication and Fundamental Electronic